britinfo.net 2016-11-03

# Privacy Statement

[UK Information](http://www.britinfo.net/ "Britain") » **Privacy Statement**

### Privacy Statement

#### Information Collection

##### Information Collection

web-site-factory.com is the sole owner of the information collected on www.britinfo.net. web-site-factory.com may collect information from users on our web site in circumstances outlined below.

Should a user feel that they would like to find out the information stored about them a request should be sent to us, in writing, and we will produce a report of the information about the user.

We do not and will not, sell or transfer any personal details about our users to any third party for the purpose of using that information for marketing or direct sales.

##### Registration

New users may need to have personal information collected and registered before they can use certain facilities and add data to the site. During registration a user is required to provide contact information such as name and e-mail address. We may use this information to contact the user about their data entries on the site such as when we have trouble processing information they submitted on-line. In future we may also use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which they have expressed an interest.

##### E-mail Updates

Users may want to receive regular updates when data on the site is updated. We need to store personal information such as name and e-mail address to be able to send them regular updates. Additionally we may store the type of information they requested. This profile is used to direct pertinent information to them. We do not share your profile with other third parties. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the Choice and Opt-out sections

#### Information Use

##### Cookies

A cookie is a small files of data that we send to your computer when we want to store some information that may be used on subsequent visits to this site.

We do not store users' personal information in cookies. Cookies may be used to store and retrieve information on individual users that details their previous on-line choices and personal preferences on how information is presented to them This information is used to tailor a user's visit to our web site, and to direct features to them. We do not share your information with other third parties.

When a user clicks on a link or advertisement for an external site, the external site may use cookies. Users should check the particular web site regarding privacy.

##### Log Files

Like most standard web site servers we use log files. This includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyse trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

#### Information storage & security

##### Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our web site.

##### Third Party Intermediaries

We use outside companies (web sites) to provide supplementary services such as on-line ticket bookings. Users should read the privacy policy on the third party's web site, if they are concerned about use of their personal information.

##### Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the information for un-subscribing contained in the e-mails.

##### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, web-site-factory.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

##### Security

This web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

All of our users' information is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to relevant personally identifiable information.

If users have any questions about the security at our web site, users can contact us using the contact information below.

##### Purchasing History

When a user makes a purchase we do not collect information about the purchases made. If a purchase is made from a third party site we are not responsible for the information that particular site stores, nor how it is used. Users should check the external site's own privacy statement.

##### Children's Privacy

We take protecting the privacy of children very seriously. We will not store, publish or use personal information where we know a person to be under 18 without the permission of a parent or guardian. Any postings to our site by a person under eighteen should be authorised by a parent or guardian.

##### Public Forums and classified advertising

This site makes classified advertisements, chat rooms, and forums available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

##### Correcting, Updating, Deleting or Deactivating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes, or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can usually be done on-line or by contacting our user support department by e-mail or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

##### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

##### Acceptance of Our Privacy Statement

By using our site or services, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Statement. We reserve the right to add to, delete from, update, modify or otherwise change this Privacy Statement at any time, and will notify you of such modifications as outlined above. Your continued use of any portion of our services following such notification will constitute your acceptance of those modifications.

##### Contact Information

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at webmaster@britinfo.net
